#### Contact

noemi.estrada5@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/noemiestrada-cantu-mba-hcm-bsnrn-81753b128 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Nursing Neurology Rehabilitation

### Languages

Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

# Noemi Estrada-Cantu MBA-HCM, BSN, RN

Nurse Manager at Michael E. DeBakey VA Medical Center Houston, Texas Area

## Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Acute Care, Stroke Rehabilitation, Nursing, Medical-Surgical, and Direct Patient Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.) focused in Health Care Management from University of Texas at Tyler.

## Experience

U.S. Department of Veterans Affairs 6 years 8 months

Nurse Manager April 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months) Houston Texas

Assistant Nurse Manager December 2013 - April 2018 (4 years 5 months) Houston, Texas Area

Michael E. DeBakey Veterans Affairs Medical Center in Houston 13 years

Registered Nurse /Neuro/ Rehab/ Medical-Surgical January 2010 - Present (10 years 7 months)

LVN

August 2007 - December 2009 (2 years 5 months)

### Education

University of Texas at Tyler

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Health/Health Care Administration/Management · (2014 - 2016)

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Nursing Science (2011 - 2013)

San Jacinto College
Associate of Science (A.S.), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2007 - 2009)